Guide to the American Institute of Sacred Literature Records 1880-1943
University of Chicago Library
- Miscellaneous articles, "The American Institute of Sacred Literature, a Historical Sketch, 1881-1902" by John Henry Barrows, reprinted from the Biblical World, March 1902 "A History of the American Institute of Sacred Literature, Part I, The American Institute of Hebrew" by Richard Myers, March 26, 1943, typescript, 22 pp. " A History of the American Institute of Sacred Literature, Part II, The American Institute of Sacred Literature," typescript, 29 pp., 2 copies (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous publications of the AISL, Postal Bulletin to the Members of the Bible Students' Reading Guild, nos. 4 and 7, 1898 Five-Minutes Leaflets, undated Gilkey, C. W., "What is Inspiration?," undated Harvey, BCH, "The Religion of an Anatomist," undated Mathews, S., "The Modernist Believes," undated Mathews, S., "Christ's Interpretation of His Second Coming, undated" Popular Religion Leaflets, undated Fosdick, H. E., "Religion Plus Intelligence," undated Beaven, A. W., "Positive v. Negative Goodness," undated Mathews, S., "Why Denominations?," undated Popular Religion leaflets, Bible Series, undated "The Sermon on the Mount," undated "The letter to the Galatians," undated Popular Religion leaflets, Good-will Series, undated Hough, L. H., "Good-will Between Churches," undated Popular Religion leaflets, Science and Religion Series, undated Schmucker, S. C., "Through Science to God," undated Conklin, E. G., "Evolution and the Bible," undated Mather, Kirtley, "The Religion of a Geologist," undated Popular Religion leaflets, Why I Believe Series, undated Brown, W. A., "Why I Believe in God," undated Macintosh, D. C., "Why I Believe in Immortality," undated Stifler, J. M., "Why I Believe in Worship," undated Supplementary catalogue of books as of September 1940 "A Short History of Christianity; a new study course," advertising circular, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)